>> 凯尔: 我多年来一直用一个比喻为我工作
&gt;&gt; Kyle: One metaphor that I have used for
years that works well for me and
也许能为你做得好
maybe will work well for you.
嵌套在彼此之间的作用域的概念与建筑物相似
This idea of scopes being nested within
each other is similar to a building
电梯里有个大电梯好吗
with a big tall elevator in it, okay?
想象一下如果你去了一栋楼而你在找东西
Imagine if you went into a building and
you were looking for something but
你不知道那是什么地方
you didn't know where it was.
你就知道是在大楼里的某个地方
You just knew it was
somewhere in the building or
大概是在这栋楼的某个地方
probably somewhere in the building.
你先从第一层开始
You'd start on the first floor.
你只是做个线性搜索
You just do basically a linear search.
从第一层开始，在那里寻找。
Start on the first floor,
look for it there.
如果你找不到它把电梯到下一层
And if you don't find it,
take the elevator to the next floor,
在那儿找
look for it there.
如果你找不到它再一次重复一次
If you don't find it,
do that again and again and again.
最终你会到达建筑物的顶层
And eventually you're gonna arrive
at the top floor of the building.
要么你要么找到要么不去但是没有别的地方可以去了
And you either find it or you don't,
but there's nowhere else to go.
所以从概念上来说，第一层是我们目前的范围，
So conceptually the first floor is our
current scope where the reference is,
顶楼是全球范围
and the top floor is the global scope.
>> 凯尔: 我们稍后会回到这个比喻。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: We'll come back to this
metaphor a later time in the course.
所以如果你想的话就把它放在你的脑袋里
So just kinda keep that in your
head if that works for you,
一次一个楼层的想法
this idea of going one floor up at a time.
我们不直接跳到全球范围，我们只需要一次发言。
We don't immediately jump to the global
scope, we just go one floor at a time.